(Laughter) And I was now writing the headlines. My favorite one was, "The stag trampled on my throat, and the press trampled on my privacy." It was the most read piece of BBC News online that day. And I was kind of having fun. And by the end of my week of media, I started to use my newfound voice and platform to spread a message of love and kindness. And when I had the minute of anger and hatred towards those press and journalists, I had to identify my inner bigotry towards them. And I had to meet and speak with these people without judgment. I had to let myself understand them, and in return, they began to understand me. Well, six months later, they asked me to join the committee that regulates the press. And a few times a year, I sip tea and dip biscuits with the likes of Daily Mail editor Paul Dacre, who says to me, "So, Kate, how have your last few months been?" And I respect them. And I'm now one of three members of the public who has a seat at the table -- not because I'm different, but because my voice counts, just like anybody else. And the irony is, every now and again, I'm asked to visit those printing presses of this declining industry, because some people think that the technology I spoke about here, last time at TED, my interactive print, might actually help save them. So beware of your inner bigot, and make friends from your enemies. Thank you. (Applause)
(Rires) J'écrivais les gros titres. Mon préféré, c'est : « Un cerf m'a piétiné la gorge, et la presse a piétiné ma vie privée. » Ce fut le titre le plus lu sur le site BBC News ce jour-là. Cela m'amusait. Au bout de ma semaine dans les médias, J'ai utilisé cette nouvelle voix et plateforme pour diffuser un message d'amour et de gentillesse. Lorsque, au début, j'avais ressenti cette haine et cette colère contre les journalistes, il a fallu que je reconnaisse mes propres préjugés à leur égard. Je les ai rencontrés, je leur ai parlé sans porter de jugement. Il a fallu que j'accepte de les comprendre. En retour, ils ont commencé à me comprendre. Six mois plus tard, ils m'ont demandé de rejoindre un comité qui réglemente la presse. Plusieurs fois par an, je bois du thé et je trempe des biscuits avec, par exemple, Paul Dacre, éditeur du Daily Mail, qui me dit : « Kate, comment se sont passés ces derniers mois ? » Je respecte ces gens. Je fais partie des trois membres du public à prendre place à cette table -- pas parce que suis différente, mais parce ma voix compte, comme celle de tout le monde. L'ironie, c'est qu'on me demande parfois de visiter les imprimeries de cette industrie sur le déclin, car certains pensent que la technologie dont j'ai parlé ici sur TED, mes publications interactives, pourraient les sauver. Méfiez-vous donc de vos préjugés, et faites de vos ennemis des alliés. Merci (Applaudissements)